Contact

- **1** +212 680096104
- abdo.zad.raja2@gmail.com
- in zadelkhair abdelkoddous
- f zadelkhair abdelkoddous

Skills

BACKEND

LARAVEL PHP REST API SQL LITE SQL



FRONTEND

VUEJS JAVASCRIPT HTML CSS BOOTSTRAP VUEX



DATABASE

SQL SERVER MY SQL ORACLE DB SQL LITE FIREBASE



MODELING

UML MERISE



DISKTOP

C# .NET JAVA JAVAFXML



MOBILE

JAVA ANDROID FIREBASE



ABDELKODDOUS

ZADELKHAIR

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Profile

My name is ABDELKODDOUS ZADELKHAIR I'm 21 years old, full stack web developer (LARAVEL & VUEJS) with a vast array of knowledge in many different front end and back end languages, responsive frameworks, databases, desktop and mobile applications (C# and JAVA). and best coding practices.

Education

2020 - 2021

Bachelor

University IBN ZOHR, AGADIR software development

2017 - 2020

Specialized Technician's Diploma

ISTICG OFPPT, Berrechid it development

2016 - 2017

Height School Diploma AWLAD HRIZ, Berrechid

Experience

2016 - Present

ALKHAYRAT

Software Development, Berrechid Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.

Consulted with engineering team members to determine system loads and develop improvement plans.

2021 - Present

TUTOREX (tutorex.org)

backend developer, Berrechid TUTOREX, school management course online With laravel and vuejs

2021

Freelancer

Desktop Application, Tiznit parking management system, with JAVAFXML, MAVEN, MYSQL

2021

Code permis

Mobile Developper, Berrechid Code permis , android application with Java and SQLite

Skills

OTHER

NPM GIT WEBPACK EXCEL ACCESS WORD POWERPOINT PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR



2020

2020

2019

2018

CODE ALKHAYRAT

Web Developer, Berrechid CODE ALKHAYRA , with laravel/vuejs and graphql

DENTAL CARE

Web Developer, Berrechid dental care, Web application with LARAVEL and VUE|S

KORA-START

Web Developer, Berrechid kora-start, Soccer new website With laravel

ISTICG

Desktop Application, Berrechid timetable management, desktop application with c# and sql server